<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="navigation_back">Back</string>
    <string name="city">Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="theater">Theater</string>
    <string name="res">Restaurent</string>
    <string name="univer">University</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="loc">Location</string>
    <string name="navigation_bottom">Navigation Bottom</string>
    <string name="cafe1"> Bidri</string>
    <string name="cafe2"> Mist The Poolside Kitchen</string>
    <string name="cafe3"> Yi Jing</string>
    <string name="cafe4"> Mekong</string>
    <string name="cafe5"> Amara</string>
    <string name="cafe1d">Hyderabad Marriott Hotel, 1-3-1024, Tank Bund Opp Hussain Sagar Lake, Hyderabad 500080 India</string>
    <string name="cafe2d">Sagar Mahal Complex Gandipet, R R District, Near Financial District, Osman Sagar Lake, Hyderabad 500075 India</string>
    <string name="cafe3d">Plot No.5 Survey No.83/1 Opposite Inorbit Mall, Hyderabad 500081 India</string>
    <string name="cafe4d">7-1-25, Green Lands, Begumpet Rd Marigold by Greenpark Hotel, Lobby Level, Hyderabad 500016 India</string>
    <string name="cafe5d">HITEC City Lobby Level P5, Trident Hotel Hyderabad, Near Cyber Towers, Hyderabad 500081 India</string>
    <string name="mov1"> Inorbit Mall</string>
    <string name="mov2"> The Forum Sujana Mall</string>
    <string name="mov3"> GVK One Mall</string>
    <string name="mov4"> Sarath City</string>
    <string name="mov5"> City Center Mall</string>
    <string name="mov1d">Inorbit Mall, situated in the IT hub of Madhapur, is renowned as one of Hyderabad’s largest and finest shopping destinations. With over 1 million square feet of retail space, the mall offers a diverse shopping experience, featuring international and national fashion brands, a multiplex cinema, numerous restaurants, a lively atmosphere, and amenities like a food court and children’s play area.</string>
    <string name="mov2d">Forum Sujana Mall, situated in Kukatpally, stands as one of Hyderabad’s largest shopping complexes. Boasting over 800,000 square feet of retail space, it offers a diverse shopping experience featuring international and national fashion brands, a multiplex cinema, a range of dining options, and convenient amenities like a food court and children’s play area.</string>
    <string name="mov3d">GVK One Mall stands as Hyderabad’s premier shopping destination, boasting a vast 1.5 million square feet of retail space. Nestled in the upscale Banjara Hills, it offers an array of international and national fashion brands, a multiplex movie theatre, diverse dining options, a food court, and a children’s play area.</string>
    <string name="mov4d">Sarath City Capital Mall is situated in Hyderabad\'s technology corridor - Hi-Tech City, Gachibowli - Miyapur Road. Sarath City Capital Mall has everything from Prestigious International brands to Local Niche brands that serve the customer in various ways.</string>
    <string name="mov5d">Located at the heart of the city, as it is defined by its name, the City Centre Mall is a wholesome package for a great outing with you folks. This is one of the best malls in Hyderabad. This 5 storied mall covers a wide variety of stores ranging from clothes to food. The parking facility provided at the basement for both two-wheelers and four-wheelers, might not be large enough for a jam-packed weekend, however, there are no parking charges.</string>
    <string name="uni1"> University of Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="uni2"> IIT Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="uni3"> IIIT Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="uni4"> Osmania University</string>
    <string name="uni5"> IFHE Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="uni1d">Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Telangana 500046. Established in 1974, it offers a wide range of postgraduate and research programs across sciences, humanities, and social sciences, with a campus spanning 2,300 acres.</string>
    <string name="uni2d">Kandi, Sangareddy, Telangana 502285Founded in 2008, this premier engineering institute offers undergraduate, postgraduate, and doctoral programs and is known for its research and innovation.</string>
    <string name="uni3d">Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Telangana 500032Established in 1998,it focuses on IT and related fields, with notable research contributions and various innovation labs.</string>
    <string name="uni4d">Osmania University Main Rd, Amberpet, Hyderabad, Telangana 500007.Founded in 1918, it offers diverse programs across disciplines and is known for its historical significance and academic excellence.</string>
    <string name="uni5d">Dontanapally, Shankarpally Road, Hyderabad, Telangana 501203. Established in 2008, it offers programs in management, science, law, and humanities, with strong infrastructure and industry connections.</string>
    <string name="loc1"> Charminar</string>
    <string name="loc2"> Golconda Fort</string>
    <string name="loc3"> Nehru Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="loc4"> Hussain Sagar Lake</string>
    <string name="loc5"> Chowmahalla Palace</string>
    <string name="loc1d">Among the most recognizable monuments in India, Charminar (char = four, minar = tower) is an ancient mosque built over 400 years ago by the Qutb Shahi dynasty after a plague forced them to shift their empire from Golconda to the new city of Hyderabad.</string>
    <string name="loc2d">Built atop a 120m-high granite hill, this imposing citadel reached its peak glory under the Qutb Shahis. It was famous for its diamond mines, in fact the legendary Kohinoor is said to have been mined here.</string>
    <string name="loc3d">Also known as Hyderabad Zoo, this tourist attraction is located right next to the Mir Alam Tank and houses over 150 species of birds, animals and reptiles.</string>
    <string name="loc5d">Once the erstwhile residence of the Nizams, this stunning complex features four magnificent palaces, vintage galleries, sprawling courtyards and lush gardens inspired by Persian and Indo-Saracenic designs.</string>
    <string name="loc4d">Built during the reign of Ibrahim Quli Shah in 1563, this heart-shaped lake is a historic city landmark and makes for an ideal recreational spot for picnics and family outings.</string>
    <string name="mus1"> Salar Jung Museum</string>
    <string name="mus2"> Chowmahalla Palace</string>
    <string name="mus3"> Nizams Museum</string>
    <string name="mus4"> Birla Science Museum</string>
    <string name="mus5"> Telangana State Archaeology Museum</string>
    <string name="mus1d">Darul Shifa, Hyderabad, Telangana 500002 , Houses a vast art collection from around the world.</string>
    <string name="mus2d">20-4-236, Motigalli, Khilwat, Hyderabad, Telangana 500002 , Former royal residence with elegant architecture and artifacts.</string>
    <string name="mus3d">Purani Haveli, Pathar Gatti, Hyderabad, Telangana 500002 , Exhibits gifts and artifacts from the Nizams era.</string>
    <string name="mus4d">Adarsh Nagar, Hyderabad, Telangana 500063 , Science exhibits, planetarium, and dinosaurium for education.</string>
    <string name="mus5d">Public Gardens, Nampally, Hyderabad, Telangana 500001 , Displays artifacts from ancient civilizations and local history.</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="Details">Details</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="profile">Prasuk</string>
    <string name="tab_inbox">Inbox</string>
    <string name="tab_sent">Sent</string>
    <string name="tab_drafts">Drafts</string>
    <string name="tab_spam">Spam</string>
    <string name="lol">lol</string>
</resources>